Are you in position?
All set.
Thank you.
Hey. The trunk.
What are you doing, slowpoke?
He’s here.
That’s Ishikawa,
the president of River Productions.
He’s got that same sleazy face as always.
Alright, Habu, I’m counting on you.
-Here is your room key.
-Thanks.
Enjoy your stay.
-What are you doing? Leave already.
-I'm sorry.
Sir, I will guide you to your room.
No, thank you. It's all right.
-I'll carry your luggage.
-I'm fine.
-Please, allow me--
-I told you…
I don't need help.
My apologies.
Seriously!
Leave it to me.
Oh, excuse me.
-Which floor?
-18th floor, please.
Thank you.
-The 19th floor.
-Understood.
The 19th floor, right? Heading there now.
Room 1926.
His room key is in
the left back pocket of his pants.
-Ow! Hey!
-Ouch!
Oh no, my racing tickets!
Watch it, idiot.
Huh? My winning ticket is gone.
-Hey! Did you take it?
-I didn't. What the heck?
-That's my phone.
-Your back pockets.
Hey, that's creepy, man.
-Huh?
-Don't take my wallet!
-I don't know about your ticket!
-Oh, sorry!
I found it.
Sorry.
Is this really okay?
It's fine.
It's locked!
Four, one, zero.
Two, two, three.
That's the code he usually uses.
Four, one, zero.
Two, two, three.
It's open.
Now…
HIKARI TAKENAKA
Nakazaki, where is the fingerprint film?
I've seen this in anime,
but it actually works?
Do you always do this sort of thing?
It's a life hack.
TRANSFERRING DATA
I'm so glad Hikari
got to star in that commercial.
Thank you as always.
It's all thanks to you, Mr. Tajima.
I'm sure Nishiguchi is happy too.
He's her manager, after all.
He's useless,
so I was thinking of replacing him soon.
Excuse me.
I brought your drinks.
Just set them down here.
Oh, understood, sir.
-My son's calling.
-Go ahead.
Hey, give me a break, you bastard!
-I'm so sorry!
-Get me a towel.
-A towel?
-You have one right there!
I do, sorry.
-What are you doing?
-I'm so sorry.
-That's too many towels!
-Sorry.
How is Yuuki doing?
Sorry. Today is canceled.
Let's reschedule.
Why so suddenly?
Mr. Tajima!
I'm sorry.
-So sorry.
-That's enough.
Excuse me. I'm sorry!
Hello?
Sorry. I'll get changed and head over.
Okay.
I'm sorry. My apologies.
S-Sabayama here! I'm sorry.
Ishikawa went back to his room!
Why so soon?
-How much time is left?
-Three minutes remaining.
I'll leave the rest to you.
-Hey, hold on!
-Where are you going?
Mr. Uramawashi, what should we do?
Are you listening?
We're still copying the files.
MINUTES LEFT
Huh?
There you are!
I accidentally picked up your key earlier.
I'm sorry.
What?
Why give him the key?
Seriously…
I am very sorry.
You too, sir?
There is currently an issue
with the room keys.
Please replace it at the front desk.
Are you serious?
We apologize for the inconvenience.
We are very sorry.
Of course it's a fake.
ONE MINUTE LEFT
DATA TRANSFER COMPLETE
-You should have told us.
-Sorry.
Good work, everyone.
The damages trial between
Mr. Shuto Ishikawa,
president of an entertainment agency,
and the defendant, a former manager,
is about to begin.
Mr. Ishikawa,
you claim that because Hikari Takenaka,
a talent under your agency,
dropped out of a commercial
due to Mr. Nishiguchi harassing her,
your agency had to pay
100 million yen in penalties. Correct?
That's right.
Because of him, our entire agency
is being slandered online.
That's strange.
It differs from Mr. Nishiguchi's claim.
That means one of you is lying.
I'm the victim here!
-Obviously, Nishiguchi is the one lying!
-No!
Your Honor.
I would like to submit
additional evidence.
COMPANY APP "RVPRO"
HAS BEEN FOUND TO BE SPYWARE
HIKARI TAKENAKA
WHY DO YOU HAVE THOSE PHOTOS? DELETE THEM
WE CAN LEAK THEM, THEN?
Why do you have this data?
You were blackmailing Hikari
and other actors,
forcing them into work against their will.
Your Honor, this has no relevance
to the case at hand.
Defense counsel, please continue.
For those who didn't comply,
you used this data to threaten them.
WE CAN LEAK THEM, THEN?
TO QUIT, PAY THE FIVE MILLION YEN
PLEASE DON'T RELEASE THAT VIDEO
No! This isn't true!
They say that to maintain one lie,
you need twenty more.
Scumbags who think nothing
of sacrificing others…
shouldn't try to lie.
Scumbags?
Only a perfected lie
can overcome the truth.
That is all from me.
If you keep at this, you'll lose
your license to practice someday.
Mr. Uramawashi, do you have a moment?
Do you plan to pursue
the Ishikawa case further?
There are accusations that
you obtained the evidence illegally!
Please answer us!
The truth was painted over with lies.
All I did was use lies to reclaim it.
Habu! Carry this!
But you lost at rock-paper-scissors.
Because of that plan, my work's piling up.
Don't spill water
on the target again, okay?
-It succeeded, so what's the problem?
-Well, that's because I had your back.
Bastard.
Hey, how many times do I have to tell you!
It's always the same thing!
CUBE HOTEL INFILTRATION PLAN
Nakazaki, congrats on your debut.
You have a knack for this.
I only wanted a normal
part-time job at a law firm.
Boss, once again,
we are deeply in the red.
Well, all necessary expenses,
to bring smiles to people's faces!
Victory drinks sure taste good.
Drinking is fine,
but please do your work properly.
This!
We haven't even finished
the initial blueprints!
I'm talking to you too, Habu!
-It's time to head home.
-What?
-See you.
-Bye.
Wait, we're still working, so help us out.
We don't pay overtime.
Wait, I don't get paid either?
Sorry, my hours are discretionary.
Well then, bye.
-Wait!
-See you.
Mr. Uramawashi!
Is the plan revision ready yet?
Being a lawyer is fine,
but please focus
on the architecture side too.
This is it.
No, this one…
-Hey.
-Guggenheim, as designed by Gehry.
These curves are so pretty,
no matter how many times I look at them.
I knew it,
we gotta go with an organic form.
No!
Whether as a lawyer or an architect,
shouldn't client preferences
come before your own tastes?
Hey, work before drinking.
Rushing won't produce
anything good, right?
No, not until I finish work! Habu!
-Bring that over.
-Huh?
-Can I just eat first…
-Hurry up!
In the end, we couldn't get
Representative Tajima.
He left so suddenly.
He's got the devil's luck.
By the way, he won again.
-Won what?
-Shuto Ishikawa's trial.
Mr. Uramawashi won brilliantly.
I don't accept him as a lawyer.
His hair is long,
and he doesn't dress properly in court.
Well, that part is problematic.
But he's protecting his clients,
so as a lawyer, isn't he a good one?
Even so, his methods are not just.
Yukari, you are too serious.
As a lawyer, that's a weakness.
Oh, look at the time.
-I'm off.
-Yukari, wait!
-Good luck.
-Yes!
President of River Productions…
He made a mess of things.
Now is an important period for me.
I don't want any unnecessary trouble.
All the cleanup
has already been completed.
Oh. I'm glad you're a competent secretary.
-Our next story is…
-Unlike some incompetent lawyer I know!
-The murder of Ms. Chiharu Aoi, 24…
-Why was he even recommended?
Padam Garty, an Ulgovian, living in Ota,
has been indicted for murder.
So far, he has denied all accusations.
SUSPECT CLAIMS
"I DIDN'T DO IT, I KNOW NOTHING"
Nice to meet you, Mr. Padam.
I am attorney Yukari Aso.
I will be your defense attorney.
I didn't kill anyone.
But the apartment CCTV
captured you, right?
I only went there to deliver a package.
No one believes me, not even the police.
I believe you.
So please, believe in me too.
-Hello.
Ms. Aso!
Mr. Moriki wants you to go to his office.
-Falsely accused?
-Yes, he denies committing the crime.
For the prosecutors to decide to indict,
they must have a lot of evidence.
But this case feels rushed
and based on circumstantial evidence.
You always charge ahead
with your sense of justice,
but can you stop that already?
Before long, you will…
Ouch.
Thanks to you, Ms. Aso,
I have to keep stomach medicine on me.
Please take care of yourself. Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello!
MR. PADAM GARTY
MURDER CASE
This case…
You have a 0.1% chance of winning.
We can win one in a thousand times.
Protecting the client
is the only correct answer for a lawyer.
No chance of you giving up I see.
JUSTICE'S FORM
Here.
I want a bit more openness.
I will look into removing the partition.
Also, I want to add more pillars.
Pillars?
Okay. What are the hiring conditions?
Smart, able to read the room,
and good at lying.
Understood. I will contact them.
-Sabayama.
-Yes?
Could you show me
that security camera footage?
The police took the footage.
But there's a backup, right?
That was taken as well.
"To preserve evidence," they said.
I see.
Then, please show me the crime scene.
There's a breaker there?
The resident liked to keep it hidden.
How was the body when found?
She didn't show up for work,
so people from the club got worried
and came to check.
She worked as a hostess, right?
Yes.
She was found collapsed,
bleeding from her head.
Right over there.
What was Ms. Chiharu like at the club?
Chiharu was flirty, so customers often got
the wrong idea and hit on her.
But she actually had a boyfriend.
She was in a relationship?
Yes. She was always bragging
that she was dating a bigshot's son.
And on social media,
she was often hinting at it.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure there was a photo of him…
What kind of person was her boyfriend?
He is the son of a Diet member,
Tajima something?
-You shouldn't tell her that.
-He was a politician's son?
Yes. At first she kept it a secret,
but she wanted to brag so badly.
It was totally obvious.
-Saki, you have a customer.
-Oh, okay!
Sorry, I was asked for.
Wait a moment.
-Um…
-I wasn't close with Chiharu at all.
-This is Saki!
-Hi, Saki!
Thank you!
Have a seat here.
-I'LL VISIT AGAIN WHEN THINGS CALM DOWN
-REALLY? IT'S A PROMISE!
A LAWYER CAME TO THE CLUB
SHE WAS ASKING ABOUT CHIHARU
Shiori, you ask him too.
-No.
-I need to give it some thought.
The victim was apparently
in a relationship with Yuuki Tajima,
Representative Tajima's son.
They planned for marriage.
-You suspect him based on that?
-I am only discussing the possibility.
-Don't look too much into this case.
-Why?!
Consider who the players are.
If you act recklessly,
it's not just you on the line.
So you're saying we should just discard
people who are vulnerable?
You want me to overlook
powerful people preying on the weak?
What is questioned in court
is not righteousness,
but facts built up from evidence.
If you misunderstand that,
you cannot save your client.
On the night of the incident, Yuuki Tajima
was having dinner with his father,
Representative Tajima.
HAVING DINNER WITH DAD TO CATCH UP
FAMILY TIME IS NICE ONCE IN A WHILE (LOL)
Dad, I'm sorry.
I had no idea a paparazzi was after me.
Please sue this weekly magazine.
Someone told me a weirdo came
to that club, asking questions.
Very well.
I'll prepare the lawsuit.
You two, don't do anything!
I'll ask this guy to handle it.
Uramawashi?
But at the recent trial, he was the one--
I'm willing to make allies out of enemies.
That's my creed.
Compared to those losers,
he is much more promising.
If we throw enough money at him,
Uramawashi will work for us.
A 30 percent markup, then.
30 percent, huh?
If we include all your requests,
it seems it will
slightly exceed your budget.
It might be a bit over budget.
We can adjust based
on what you prioritize,
so let's discuss it together.
My fee is triple the market rate.
Is that acceptable?
Huh? Triple?
His fees are extortion.
I recommend you stay away from him.
I will hear the details when I visit.
Thank you very much.
I didn't expect you to accept our offer.
I will not disappoint.
Next, Exhibit No.7.
This is security camera footage
from the victim's apartment.
The defendant is seen entering and leaving
shortly before the victim's time of death,
and with this evidence,
we plan to prove the defendant's guilt.
After that, no one else was seen
entering or leaving the area.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
I was saving this seat.
What are you talking about?
My bag… Right, my bag!
I left my bag here.
Do you have any proof?
Proof?
If you don't, stop making stuff up.
I'm very sorry.
There is proof.
Huh? Mr. Uramawashi?
How do you know of me?
I am a lawyer too.
So?
I'm asking where her proof is.
That woman over there
took a selfie earlier.
Angle-wise, it caught this seat.
Also, a delivery truck passed by.
The dashcam should've caught this too.
What?
I've written down the plate number.
Shall we try contacting them?
Very well. I just need to move, right?
Only in Japan can you reserve a seat
just by leaving your bag!
It's our victory.
-Go ahead.
-You lied about the selfie.
That lady doesn't seem
like she takes selfies.
Besides,
I'm sure no delivery truck passed by.
Your observation skills aren't half-bad.
I don't want to sit in a seat
obtained through a lie.
You didn't obtain it.
You reclaimed what was yours,
through a lie.
If there were no lies in this world,
we would never have to doubt each other,
or worry about hidden intentions.
Because some people lie,
even people who do not lie
end up being suspects.
Your ideals are beautiful.
Is that a bad thing?
You are like Le Corbusier's Villa Savoye.
Something urgent came up,
so please let me reschedule.
I don't really understand. Excuse me.
I scanned all of her investigation files.
How was it?
She is not my enemy.
Oh, you seem tired.
A lot happened.
Oh, hey!
They say Yuuki Tajima is suing
this weekly magazine!
-Due to the Chiharu article.
-Yeah.
Attorney Uramawashi took the case.
Huh?
It's not related to Mr. Padam's trial,
but you never know
what they might do, so be careful.
Why did he agree
to defend Tajima's son anyway?
Wouldn't it be better to defeat the son
to help that Padam guy?
You're a real idiot, aren't you?
An idiot?
An idiot!
Even if he defeats the son, he'll miss
the main target, Representative Tajima.
He must help them in court
to gain their trust. Right?
Very good, Nakazaki.
You aren't like Sabayama.
-Thank you very much.
-Hey, I knew that too, you know.
-I was just--
-Excuse me!
-I came for an interview!
-Welcome, we've been waiting.
-Who is that?
-Nice to meet you.
She's interviewing for our next job.
-Hello.
TODAY'S TRENDING ARTICLE
Because of this article, people are
leaving comments, claiming I'm the killer.
The quickest way is to get that foreigner
named Padam to confess.
Can you do that?
He is ignorant of the law.
If we tell him we'll protect his family
from forced deportation,
he'll work with us.
That way, Yuuki's name won't be tarnished.
Excuse me.
By the way,
what were you doing
on the night of the murder?
What?
-Are you suspecting me?
-No.
In order to protect you,
I want to know the truth.
Hypothetically, even if they suspect you
are involved in the murder,
if you tell the truth,
we can get a suspended sentence.
Maybe.
Depending on the intent,
the verdict varies greatly.
I see.
Around 7:00 p.m., the time of the crime,
where were you?
On that day, after work,
I went out for dinner.
Dinner?
With whom?
Yuuki was having dinner
with Representative Tajima.
We have proof.
Chiharu was just a girl
I fooled around with.
I had no reason to kill her.
Ever been to her apartment?
No.
Not even once?
Nope.
Very well.
LEMON GASUI
It's done.
A blueprint of lies.
Ms. Konno, room B, please.
The most expensive spot.
-Habu, take the dimensions from the model.
-Got it. I'll draft the layouts.
Is this 1 to 30?
Match it with the wall surface.
-I know.
-Nakazaki, samples for the cross-panels.
Okay.
Sabayama, verify the materials
and list interior finishes and equipment.
-Okay.
-Oh, right. Ms. Konno.
Handle this too.
What is this for?
-Won't concrete work for the aging finish?
-I know.
-Search online for the circled parts here.
-Excuse me.
I am Yukari Aso,
an attorney from Cordia Law Firm.
Huh?
Wait, is this Mr. Uramawashi's office?
Mr. Uramawashi is in that room.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry.
Have we met somewhere before?
-No. This is our first meeting.
-No…
-I've met you--
-Why have you come to see him?
-I will guide you.
-No need.
Mr. Uramawashi. Excuse me!
I am Yukari Aso,
an attorney from Cordia Law Firm.
I met you the other day.
Mr. Padam suddenly confessed.
What on earth did you say to him?
The person who killed Chiharu Aoi
might be Yuuki Tajima.
They used influence
to pin the crime on Mr. Padam.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm in the middle of an interview.
This lawyer is calling me a killer.
I'm going to sue her for defamation!
What?
Why her and not the publisher?
It will show them we mean business.
Wait a minute.
What if this creates more trouble?
Making an enemy out of a lawyer--
Don't interfere!
Mr. Uramawashi.
I leave this up to you.
TOKYO DISTRICT COURT
INDICTMENT
DEFENDANT - YUKARI ASO
Ms. Aso, don't worry.
Even if you lose the trial, it's okay.
It's not like your life is over.
Just do your best.
No, I can't help.
I'm insanely busy right now.
It's fine.
I will defend myself.
What wins in court is not influence,
but justice, right?
Thanks for waiting!
I'm here.
Sorry, my mistake!
There you are!
I got plenty of cute girls
for you, Mr. Uramawashi.
Why thank you.
I'll stick with you all night.
Alright, then,
as a rally before the decisive battle,
everyone's drinking tonight!
Yay! Cheers!
-First time here?
-Yes.
I'm Ai. Nice to meet you.
-Nice, Ai! Let's toast!
-Hang on!
-Here, Ai.
-May I?
-Cheers.
Hey, Yuuki.
Let's go home together.
Should we?
Sorry, I'll head out first!
Mr. Uramawashi, I'm heading out.
-Allow me to drive you two home.
-Really?
I haven't drunk.
-How nice!
-You mean it?
-Well then, please do.
-Huh?
Ai?
Huh?
What?
This room…
Will you be all right tomorrow?
At the last hearing,
I pointed out traces of editing
in the apartment's CCTV footage,
and they haven't been able to explain it.
I believe they edited the footage
to remove Yuuki Tajima from it.
Then, you will go all out.
Yes!
We will now begin the witness examination.
Regarding the CCTV footage
claim made by the defendant last time,
we have Mr. Igawa,
the apartment manager, joining us.
You were habitually committing mail theft.
In order to erase that evidence,
you edited the security camera footage.
What?
I am very sorry.
There is no footage remaining
from the day of the incident.
Correct.
Objection!
Are you covering for someone?
Please speak truthfully.
I'm not lying!
It's the truth.
PLAINTIFF EXAMINATION
We will now begin
the examination of the plaintiff himself.
Plaintiff's counsel, please proceed.
Mr. Tajima,
the defendant stated to a reporter
that you murdered Chiharu Aoi.
Is this true or false?
False.
You have never been to her place either.
Of course not.
Your Honor,
may I ask questions using Exhibit No.5?
Granted.
Huh? This…
This room is an exact recreation
of the room where Ms. Aoi lived,
before she was murdered.
What is the meaning of this?
I took the liberty of testing you
based on my judgment.
Testing?
It is to protect you.
Hypothetically, if Mr. Tajima
had murdered Ms. Aoi,
waking up and realizing he is at her place
should make him agitated, but!
Take a look.
He is completely calm.
He is clearly agitated.
Huh?
Then, inconveniently, a blackout happened.
He is obviously agitated, isn't he?
-Why does he know where the breaker is?
-Please don't speak out of line.
You just happened
to see the breaker, right?
That's right.
Even when running out of the room,
the plaintiff avoided a specific spot!
That is the spot where
Ms. Aoi was found dead.
You have been there before!
Please do not speak out of line.
Ms. Aso's statements are all forced logic.
But… You can't dismiss this
as mere coincidence.
If you want to make that claim,
there is one more
piece of evidence that solidifies
Mr. Tajima's innocence.
Mr. Igawa, the apartment manager,
deleted the CCTV footage
from the day of the murder,
to hide his own theft.
But we recovered it.
Order in the court!
If you check this,
you will see that Mr. Tajima
does not appear on camera.
Hey!
With this, your innocence will be proven.
Wait! Stop going off-script!
Order in the court!
I found it in your car the other day,
when I was driving you home.
No…
It's not mine!
Isn't that the nail that was on
Ms. Aoi's index finger?
The corpse's index finger
was missing its nail.
It came off while you were fighting?
Impossible!
There's just no way!
So the one who killed
Aoi Chiharu really was you!
That is merely your speculation.
Yuuki, calm down.
If I show this footage,
the truth will be revealed.
Your Honor, please play the video.
-She fell on her own!
-Yuuki!
-I didn't kill her!
Please wait a moment.
Does that mean
you were lying?
Am I correct?
It was an accident!
I just pushed her, and she fell,
I had no intent to kill her!
If I tell the truth,
I'll get a suspended sentence, right?
Your lies…
have no beauty to them.
Attorney Aso.
Things have taken an unexpected turn.
While I do regret it, I wish you the best.
Your Honor.
I have no further questions.
Ai, you did great.
Two envelopes?
We'll call you when we need you again.
Wait, you're paying me this much?
In the end, he was lying about restoring
the CCTV footage, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah!
That disc was empty.
The nail was also fake. We copied it
from Chiharu's social media.
By pretending to save the son,
he got close to Representative Tajima.
In doing so,
he ended up taking down both of them.
-A job well done.
-Nakazaki.
-Yes!
-Can I take all this with me?
-Sure.
-Here we go.
By the way, that alibi photo,
he knew it was fake from the start.
-Really?
-Hey, out of the way!
The road in the background…
At 7:00 p.m. that day,
there was no traffic jam.
So he knew and played along!
I'm glad he's our ally.
As an enemy, he's terrifying!
Naoto Uramawashi, you committed acts
against the interests of your client,
and violated your duty of good faith.
Pursuant to Article 56,
Paragraph One of the Attorneys Act,
you are hereby suspended from practice.
You are not fit to be a lawyer.
Do you have any last words?
Eileen Gray once said…
"To create,
one must first question everything."
That's all.
Eileen?
Who's that?
Do you know?
The Japanese branch is now on track.
Yes, impressive.
Like father, like son.
Thank you very much.
You have a guest.
Sorry to disturb your meal.
Mr. Furuse!
I am…
I am sorry for being late.
Sorry for--
My office received some photos,
sent anonymously.
-Oh.
-Along with proof of your illegal conduct.
What?
Was it Mr. Ishikawa?
So you were meeting with him?
-This…
-Are you hiding something from me?
I am very sorry!
-But--
-Please, stand up.
Your son's problem is more important.
It is no longer just your personal issue,
it could spell trouble
for our entire party.
You understand, right?
My apologies, but…
Murata.
I'll need you to come back here soon.
I understand.
-Sorry.
-Wait!
-It's no problem.
-Mr. Tajima.
Sir! Wait…
This is good!
Right?
I'm glad Mr. Padam got an acquittal.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to admit it,
but it's thanks to Mr. Uramawashi.
Is that so?
Good timing, then.
I'd like to ask you to monitor him.
Huh?
If he keeps on being reckless,
it will affect the credibility
of our bar association.
-I'm asking you, as the President--
-Wait, I can't do it!
I really can't.
Because you were sued, our office
was busy handling complaints, you know.
It was really tough!
I'll do it.
Thank you.
I'm not asking you to see him daily.
Just check on him a few days a week.
Okay.
Besides, he said you passed, too.
-What are you talking about?
-Do your best.
So, I will be visiting you starting today.
Don't fool around.
We have to start closing your office.
Delete your home page,
hide any signs you have outside.
I don't have either.
Please don't lie to me.
I was so busy suing you, Aso,
my architectural work has been piling up.
What?
Mr. Uramawashi, you are an architect?
More importantly,
when did you start lying?
Did you leak info to the weekly magazine
so that Yuuki Tajima
would request your defense?
Did you sue me in a civil trial
just to drag him to court?
Not bad.
But it's all so boring.
Please, at least answer me this.
Why did you get suspended
from being a lawyer?
For someone as sharp as you,
there must have been ways to corner
the Tajimas without being suspended!
I got tired of being a lawyer.
-What?
-That's a lie.
What?!
Right now, you are an architect,
not a lawyer!
The evidence of his violence
still remains in the video!
-He hasn't found out yet?
-I will fight fair and square and win.
If they become the main developers,
they can make a lot more money…
His lies.
I'll expose them.
Careless words invite ruin.
I'll make sure you never defend again.
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.